TeleLearning Network Inc. fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- TeleLearning Conference records, 1996 - 2001; F-172-5; 52 cm of textual records 92 sound recordings 40 artifacts; Physical description: includes 116 audio cassettes.
  - 1998 Vancouver Conference files, F-172-5-4; 2 cm of textual records 18 sound recordings; Physical description: includes 25 audio cassettes.
    - International Market Opportunities in Telelearning, 15 November 1998; F-172-5-4-0-0-4 (Audio cassette OBJ-3661)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item33.
    - Results that Surprise, 15 November 1998; F-172-5-4-0-0-5 (Audio cassette OBJ-3662)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item34.
    - The Designs of Virtual Labs and Simulations, 15 November 1998; F-172-5-4-0-0-6 (Audio cassette OBJ-3663)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item35.
    - Innovations in Canadian Colleges, 15 November 1998; F-172-5-4-0-0-7 (Audio cassette OBJ-3664)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item36.
    - The Global Educators Network: A new model for international partnerships, 16 November 1998; F-172-5-4-0-0-8 (Audio cassette OBJ-3665)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item37.
    - What's Up Down South, 16 November 1998; F-172-5-4-0-0-9 (Audio cassette OBJ-3666)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item38.
    - Workplace: Virtual Telelearning Centres, Design and Implementation, 16 November 1998; F-172-5-4-0-0-10 (Audio cassette OBJ-3667)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item39.
    - Telelearning in Practice, 16 November 1998; F-172-5-4-0-0-11 (Audio cassette OBJ-3668)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item40.
    - Making Telelearning Work for Diverse Communities, 16 November 1998; F-172-5-4-0-0-12 (Audio cassette OBJ-3669)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item41.
    - Awards banquet, 16 November 1998; F-172-5-4-0-0-13 (Audio cassette OBJ-3670)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item42.
    - Using Telelearning in Developing Countries, 17 November 1998; F-172-5-4-0-0-14 (Audio cassette OBJ-3671, Audio cassette OBJ-3672)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item43.
    - Policy Forum - Virtual universities: Dispatches from the front, 17 November 1998; F-172-5-4-0-0-15 (Audio cassette OBJ-3673, Audio cassette OBJ-3674)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item45.
    - Making the Business Case, 17 November 1998; F-172-5-4-0-0-16 (Audio cassette OBJ-3675, Audio cassette OBJ-3676)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item47.
    - K-12 Telelearning Advances, 17 November 1998; F-172-5-4-0-0-17 (Audio cassette OBJ-3677)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item49.
    - Post-secondary: New Models of Learning, New Methods of Research, 17 November 1998; F-172-5-4-0-0-18 (Audio cassette OBJ-3678)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item50.
    - TeleLearning Conference - Vancouver 1998, vol. 1, F-172-5-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 172-18)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-5-0-0-8.
    - TeleLearning Conference - Vancouver 1998, vol. 2, F-172-5-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 172-18)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-5-0-0-9.
  - 1999 Montreal Conference files, F-172-5-5; 12 cm of textual records 23 sound recordings; Physical description: includes 28 audio cassettes.
    Sub-series consists of material relating to the 1999 TeleLearning Conference held in Montreal.
    - Opening Plenary, 7 November 1999; F-172-5-5-0-0-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3679, Audio cassette OBJ-3680)
      Harasim, Linda; John Gage; Starr Roxanne Hiltz; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item51.
    - Educating the Educator State-of-the-Art, 7 November 1999; F-172-5-5-0-0-2 (Audio cassette OBJ-3681, Audio cassette OBJ-3682)
      Thérèse Laferrière; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item53.
    - Industry Snapshot: Distributed Learning Momentum, Spins and New Ventures, 7 November 1999; F-172-5-5-0-0-3 (Audio cassette OBJ-3683)
      Hamilton, Chuck; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item55.
    - Innovative Learning Applications Using Broadband Networks, 7 November 1999; F-172-5-5-0-0-4 (Audio cassette OBJ-3684)
      Rafiq Khan; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item56.
    - K-12 and Teacher Training, 7 November 1999; F-172-5-5-0-0-5 (Audio cassette OBJ-3685)
      Victor Glickman; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item57.
    - K-12 Pioneer Panel, 7 November 1999; F-172-5-5-0-0-6 (Audio cassette OBJ-3686)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item58.
    - Post-secondary Education Pioneer Panel, 7 November 1999; F-172-5-5-0-0-7 (Audio cassette OBJ-3687)
      Paul Bacsich; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item59.
    - Investing in Online Education, 8 November 1999; F-172-5-5-0-0-8 (Audio cassette OBJ-3688)
      Curry, Joanne; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item60.
    - Workplace Training Worries: Ask the Wizards, 8 November 1999; F-172-5-5-0-0-9 (Audio cassette OBJ-3689)
      Carey, Tom; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item61.
    - Leadership and Innovation in Canadian Colleges, 8 November 1999; F-172-5-5-0-0-10 (Audio cassette OBJ-3690)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item62.
    - Next Generation Telelearning Systems, 8 November 1999; F-172-5-5-0-0-11 (Audio cassette OBJ-3691, Audio cassette OBJ-3692)
      Calvert, Thomas W.; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item63.
    - An End to Student Segregation, 8 November 1999; F-172-5-5-0-0-12 (Audio cassette OBJ-3693)
      Murray Turoff; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item64.
    - State of the Art in Post-secondary, 8 November 1999; F-172-5-5-0-0-13 (Audio cassette OBJ-3694, Audio cassette OBJ-3695)
      Harasim, Linda; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item65.
    - State of the Art in K-12, 8 November 1999; F-172-5-5-0-0-14 (Audio cassette OBJ-3696)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item66.
    - Awards Banquet, 8 November 1999; F-172-5-5-0-0-15 (Audio cassette OBJ-3697)
      Coté-O'Hara, Jocelyne; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item67.
    - Evidence on the Effects of Telelearning, 9 November 1999; F-172-5-5-0-0-16 (Audio cassette OBJ-3698)
      Bereiter, Carl; Breuleux, Alain; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item68.
    - Industry ICTs for Education and Training, 9 November 1999; F-172-5-5-0-0-17 (Audio cassette OBJ-3699)
      Monique Charbonneau; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item69.
    - International Perspectives on the Cost and Benefits of Telelearning in Higher Education, 9 November 1999; F-172-5-5-0-0-18 (Audio cassette OBJ-3700)
      Tony Bates; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item70.
    - Learner Support: Providing Services to Help Telelearning Students Succeed, 9 November 1999; F-172-5-5-0-0-19 (Audio cassette OBJ-3701)
      Randy Bruce; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item71.
    - Regional and National Strategies, 9 November 1999; F-172-5-5-0-0-20 (Audio cassette OBJ-3702)
      Winters, Chris; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item72.
    - Special Guest Speaker, 9 November 1999; F-172-5-5-0-0-21 (Audio cassette OBJ-3703)
      Gilbert Paquette; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item73.
    - Teacher Professional Development: Online learning market opportunities and business models, 9 November 1999; F-172-5-5-0-0-22 (Audio cassette OBJ-3704, Audio cassette OBJ-3705)
      Vivian Fossman; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item74.
    - Who Does What: Changing Roles for Workplace TeleLearning Providers, 9 November 1999; F-172-5-5-0-0-23 (Audio cassette OBJ-3706)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item76.
    - TeleLearning Conference - Montreal 1999, vol. 1, F-172-5-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 172-18)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-5-0-0-10.
    - TeleLearning Conference - Montreal 1999, vol. 2, F-172-5-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 172-18)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-5-0-0-11.
    - TeleLearning Conference - Montreal 1999, vol. 3, F-172-5-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 172-18)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-5-0-0-12.
    - TeleLearning Conference - Montreal 1999, vol. 4, F-172-5-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 172-18)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-5-0-0-13.
    - TeleLearning Conference - Montreal 1999: promotional material, F-172-5-5-0-5 (Urc tote box 172-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item8.
  - 2000 Toronto Conference files, F-172-5-6; 11 cm of textual records 22 sound recordings; Physical description: includes 29 audio cassettes.
    Sub-series consists of material relating to the 2000 TeleLearning Conference held in Toronto.
    - Learning Object Repositories: eLearning's Next Step: Planning for Learning Content Management in Your Organization, 4 November 2000; F-172-5-6-0-0-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3707, Audio cassette OBJ-3708, Audio cassette OBJ-3709, Audio cassette OBJ-3710)
      Nick Galen; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item77.
    - Professional Development - Online Professional Development: From Tutorials to Online Communities of Inquiry, 4 November 2000; F-172-5-6-0-0-2 (Audio cassette OBJ-3711, Audio cassette OBJ-3712)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item81.
    - Measuring the Impact of Learning - Successful Technology Initiatives in Schools: How to Recognize and Build Them, 4 November 2000; F-172-5-6-0-0-3 (Audio cassette OBJ-3713, Audio cassette OBJ-3714)
      Breuleux, Alain; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item83.
    - Architecting the Virtual University: Constructing Enterprise Architectures for Distributed Learning, 5 November 2000; F-172-5-6-0-0-4 (Audio cassette OBJ-3715)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item85.
    - Telelearning Professional Development, 5 November 2000; F-172-5-6-0-0-5 (Audio cassette OBJ-3716)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item86.
    - Deploying Learning Technology in the Workplace: Current Practice and Future Directions, 5 November 2000; F-172-5-6-0-0-6 (Audio cassette OBJ-3717)
      Michael Bloom; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item87.
    - Opening Plenary - From Research to Solution / The Social Life of Information: Implications for Education, 5 November 2000; F-172-5-6-0-0-7 (Audio cassette OBJ-3718, Audio cassette OBJ-3719)
      Harasim, Linda; Paul Duguid; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item88.
    - Knowledge-based Innovation in Education: Will Canada Be Left Behind?, 5 November 2000; F-172-5-6-0-0-8 (Audio cassette OBJ-3720)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item90.
    - The Use of Wireless Technology and Handheld Devices in Education and Training, 5 November 2000; F-172-5-6-0-0-9 (Audio cassette OBJ-3721)
      Davies, Hal; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item91.
    - International Partnership Opportunities, 5 November 2000; F-172-5-6-0-0-10 (Audio cassette OBJ-3722)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item92.
    - Collective Responsibility for a New Order of Educational Achievement, 6 November 2000; F-172-5-6-0-0-11 (Audio cassette OBJ-3723, Audio cassette OBJ-3724)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item94.
    - Telelearning Methodology: Designing Efficient Training for the Workplace, 6 November 2000; F-172-5-6-0-0-12 (Audio cassette OBJ-3725)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item96.
    - Post-Secondary State of the Art: Virtual Universities and Colleges, 6 November 2000; F-172-5-6-0-0-13 (Audio cassette OBJ-3726)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item97.
    - Telelearning for Sustaining Rural Communities: The Changing Role of Small Schools in Knowledge Societies, 6 November 2000; F-172-5-6-0-0-14 (Audio cassette OBJ-3727)
      Ken Stevens; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item98.
    - Scaling Up With the Technology of the Future, 6 November 2000; F-172-5-6-0-0-15 (Audio cassette OBJ-3728)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item99.
    - Online Learning Consortia, 6 November 2000; F-172-5-6-0-0-16 (Audio cassette OBJ-3729)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item100.
    - Knowledge Stewardship: Integrating Learning and Work, 7 November 2000; F-172-5-6-0-0-17 (Audio cassette OBJ-3730)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item101.
    - Global Spotlight: Creating a Knowledge Bank, 7 November 2000; F-172-5-6-0-0-18 (Audio cassette OBJ-3731)
      Stahmer, Anna; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item102.
    - Spotlight on Latin America, 7 November 2000; F-172-5-6-0-0-19 (Audio cassette OBJ-3732)
      Diane Cantu; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item103.
    - Human Capacity Building: The Bridge Over the Digital Divide, 7 November 2000; F-172-5-6-0-0-20 (Audio cassette OBJ-3733)
      Séguin, Charles; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item104.
    - Telelearning in the Health Sector, 7 November 2000; F-172-5-6-0-0-21 (Audio cassette OBJ-3734)
      Erin Keough; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item105.
    - Faculty Involvement in Telelearning: Moving Beyond the Early Adopters, 7 November 2000; F-172-5-6-0-0-22 (Audio cassette OBJ-3735)
      Terry Anderson; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item106.
    - TeleLearning Conference - Toronto 2000, vol. 1, F-172-5-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 172-19)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-5-0-0-14.
    - TeleLearning Conference - Toronto 2000, vol. 2, F-172-5-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 172-19)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-5-0-0-15.
    - TeleLearning Conference - Toronto 2000: promotional material, F-172-5-6-0-3 (Urc tote box 172-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item9.
  - 2001 Vancouver Conference files, F-172-5-7; 12 cm of textual records 21 sound recordings; Physical description: includes 24 audio cassettes.
    Sub-series consists of material relating to the 2001 TeleLearning Conference held in Vancouver.
    - Opening Plenary 2001, 11 November 2001; F-172-5-7-0-0-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3736, Audio cassette OBJ-3737)
      Ross Paul; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item107.
    - ICTs in the Work of the Commonwealth of Learning, 11 November 2001; F-172-5-7-0-0-2 (Audio cassette OBJ-3738)
      Long, Brian; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item109.
    - Instructional Practices and Design in K-12 Online Education, 11 November 2001; F-172-5-7-0-0-3 (Audio cassette OBJ-3739)
      Muirhead, Bill; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item110.
    - Private and Public Partnerships: Models and Issues, 11 November 2001; F-172-5-7-0-0-4 (Audio cassette OBJ-3740)
      Marquis Bureau; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item111.
    - SITES-M2 and OECD International Studies of ICT Schools: Preliminary Findings, 11 November 2001; F-172-5-7-0-0-5 (Audio cassette OBJ-3741)
      Ron Owston; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item112.
    - Teledesigners / Teletrainers in the Workplace, 11 November 2001; F-172-5-7-0-0-6 (Audio cassette OBJ-3742)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item113.
    - Compelling Educational Uses of Wireless: Beyond the Wireless LAN, 11 November 2001; F-172-5-7-0-0-7 (Audio cassette OBJ-3743)
      Julie Zilber; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item114.
    - New Media, New Learning (Special Lecture), 12 November 2001; F-172-5-7-0-0-8 (Audio cassette OBJ-3744, Audio cassette OBJ-3745)
      Janet Murray; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item115.
    - Telelearning for Professional Continuing Education: Field Studies, 12 November 2001; F-172-5-7-0-0-9 (Audio cassette OBJ-3746, Audio cassette OBJ-3747)
      Gilbert Paquette; Thérèse Laferrière; Breuleux, Alain; Ileana de la Teja; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item117.
    - The Global Open Source Movement, 12 November 2001; F-172-5-7-0-0-10 (Audio cassette OBJ-3748)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item119.
    - Digital Divide, 12 November 2001; F-172-5-7-0-0-11 (Audio cassette OBJ-3749)
      Rob Mastin; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item120.
    - How Do We Know What We Know About Telelearning: Lessons Learning About Doing Research in the Field (or Workplace), 12 November 2001; F-172-5-7-0-0-12 (Audio cassette OBJ-3750)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item121.
    - Virtual Universities: Systematizing Lessons from Around the World, 12 November 2001; F-172-5-7-0-0-13 (Audio cassette OBJ-3751)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item122.
    - The Impact of New Technologies on Telelearning, 12 November 2001; F-172-5-7-0-0-14 (Audio cassette OBJ-3752)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item123.
    - Informing Practice Through Research: Successful Collaborations, 13 November 2001; F-172-5-7-0-0-15 (Audio cassette OBJ-3753)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item124.
    - Social Movement eLearning, 11 November 2001; F-172-5-7-0-0-16 (Audio cassette OBJ-3754)
      Jeff Taylor; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item125.
    - Realizing Vision for Educational Technology, 11 November 2001; F-172-5-7-0-0-17 (Audio cassette OBJ-3755)
      Malcolm Roberts; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item126.
    - Online Learning Use in Aboriginal Communities, 11 November 2001; F-172-5-7-0-0-18 (Audio cassette OBJ-3756)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item127.
    - Broadband Applications Around the World, 11 November 2001; F-172-5-7-0-0-19 (Audio cassette OBJ-3757)
      James Rossiter; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item128.
    - International Panel: Key TeleLearning Challenges in the Next Five Years, 11 November 2001; F-172-5-7-0-0-20 (Audio cassette OBJ-3758)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item129.
    - High Band Connectivity and Learning: A Step Forward or Back?, 11 November 2001; F-172-5-7-0-0-21 (Audio cassette OBJ-3759)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item130.
    - TeleLearning Conference - Vancouver 2001, vol. 1, F-172-5-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 172-19)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-5-0-0-16.
    - TeleLearning Conference - Vancouver 2001, vol. 2, F-172-5-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 172-19)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-5-0-0-17.
    - TeleLearning Conference - Vancouver 2001, vol. 3, F-172-5-7-0-3 (Archival box - standard 172-19)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-5-0-0-18.
    - TeleLearning Conference - Vancouver 2001: promotional material, F-172-5-7-0-4 (Urc tote box 172-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-172-item10.
- Research files, 1995 - 2002; F-172-6; 30 cm of textual records 17.2 mb. of textual records (electronic)
  This series consists of records relating to the administration of TeleLearning research projects by the Network management office. Activities documented include the receipt of theme and project progress reports, drafting of project proposals and contracts, distribution of research funds, and the undertaking by the management office of its own research project, the "Network of TeleLearning Communities" project.
  Records include correspondence, reports, notes and working papers, contracts, agreements and memoranda of understanding, overheads and presentations, prototype specifications, research theme and project reports, budget papers, financial statements, invoices, expense claims and supporting documentation. Record media include paper and electronic.
  Arrangement into sub-series is based on the management office's filing system.
  Reports and other records relating to TeleLearning research projects are distributed throughout the fonds; see especially the sub-series F-172-1-1, "Board of Directors meeting records" and F-172-1-3 "Program Committee meeting records."
  - Network of TeleLearning Communities project files, 1999 - 2000; F-172-6-1; 9 cm of textual records
    This sub-series consists of records relating to the management of the project. Activities documented include proposal development, Steering Committee deliberations, participant liaison, allocation of funds, and project reporting. Records include the project proposal, budgets, correspondence, meeting records, progress reports, final report, participant profiles, reports and summary financial statements. Records are retained in paper medium only.
    - Final report, 2000; F-172-6-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 172-20)
    - Financial statements, 2000; F-172-6-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 172-20)
    - Meetings and correspondence, 1999; F-172-6-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 172-20)
    - Original proposal, 1999; F-172-6-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 172-20)
    - Participant reports, vol. 1, 2000; F-172-6-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 172-20)
    - Participant reports, vol. 2, 2000; F-172-6-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 172-20)
    - Participant reports, vol. 3, 2000; F-172-6-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 172-20)
    - Participating organizations, 1999; F-172-6-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 172-20)
    - Steering Committee decisions, 1999; F-172-6-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 172-20)
  - Research theme and project reports, 1995 - 2001; F-172-6-2; 4 cm of textual records 16.9 mb. of textual records (electronic)